https://www.jackscamp.com/privacy-statement/

Professionals
Jamie K. BlairNathan J. BreseeRichard W. BryanSusan Knell BumbaloArthur D. BurgerZachary L. ChapmanDavid H. CoxWilliam E. DavisCrystal S. DeesePamela J. DiedrichChristopher P. FerragamoChristopher A. GlaserSarah E. GodfreyGlenn W.D. GoldingTiffany L. GreavesPeter J. JenkinsSathima H. JonesRoy L. KaufmannDavid L. KelleherRobert N. KellyTodd P. KendrickNancy Ortmeyer KuhnErica L. LitovitzWarren LutzDaniel J. LynnJames N. MarkelsJohn J. MatteoNicholas S. McConnellErin N. McGonagleJames R. MichalKamilah MitchellChristopher M. QuinlanDavid A. RahnisMeagan E. RoachAnnette P. RolainEdward J. SedlacekBrian W. ThompsonMarie L. VanDamKristen C. VineMitchell B.
Weitzman
Careers
PDF
Privacy Statement
Website Privacy Statement
Jackson & Campbell, P.C. is committed to protecting the privacy of visitors to this website. This policy statement describes how Jackson & Campbell collects and uses information relating to website visitors.
Cookies and Log Files
Jackson & Campbell receives non-personally identifiable information through cookies and log files when individuals access the Jackson & Campbell website. Cookies are small computer files that are transferred from our website to your computer to collect certain technical information, such as IP address, page views, operating system, web browser software, and referring and destination websites. Log files are created on our server and collect similar information, including the date and time that each IP address visits our website. These tools allow the statistical monitoring of how many people are utilizing the Jackson & Campbell website, how often it is visited and the length of stay. We use the information gathered from cookies and log files solely to generate demographic and user statistics to improve the content of its website. There is no linking of information obtained from cookies or log files to identifying personal information.
Google Analytics
In addition to the cookies and log files generated by Jackson & Campbells web server, this website uses Google Analytics, an analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (Google). The service uses cookies to help us analyze how visitors use our website. The information generated by the cookies about your use of the website (including your IP address) is transmitted to and stored by Google. Google uses this information to assess use of this website and to issue reports on website activity for website operators. Google also may transfer this information to third parties. You may refuse the use of cookies by Google Analytics and the Jackson & Campbell server by selecting the appropriate setting on your browser; please note however that declining cookies may affect your ability to access the full functionality of this or other websites.
Newsletters and Client Advisories
Apart from those who form attorney-client relationships with us, the only identifying personal information that Jackson & Campbell collects is the information that you voluntarily provide to us when, for example, you submit a request to receive newsletters or advisories, or when you contact Jackson & Campbell by e-mail. This information is used solely to address your request for information, to respond to your email or to include you on one of our mailing lists.
Information Disclosure Practices
Jackson & Campbell does not share information with any third parties without consent except as follows: (i) when disclosure is necessary to comply with the law or to protect the safety of Jackson & Campbell’s users or others, and (ii) when service providers performing services on behalf of Jackson & Campbell need access to such data as part of their work for Jackson & Campbell, and on these occasions this access is only to the extent necessary to enable them to perform their service on the firm’s behalf and they will be contractually prohibited from using the information for any other purpose.
Linked Sites
Jackson & Campbell may include links to external websites on its website from time to time. The inclusion of any link is not an endorsement of the website or its sponsor. Links are provided as a convenience and for informational purposes only. We make no representation or warranty as to the privacy policies of these websites, please refer to each websites privacy policy before using the site. Nor are we responsible for the content of any third party website.
Security
Jackson & Campbell employs industry standard security measures for its website designed to protect against loss, misuse or alteration of information; Jackson & Campbell is not responsible for unauthorized access to information by hackers or others who have obtained such access through illegal means.
Changes and Questions
Jackson & Campbell reserves the right to revise its privacy policy at any time by posting a new privacy policy at this location. Please check this page periodically for changes. Continued use of this website signifies your assent to this Privacy Statement. Should you have questions about this Privacy Statement, please send an e-mail to webmaster@jackscamp.com.
Opt-Outs
If you wish to discontinue or opt-out of any service associated with this website or to unsubscribe to any newsletter, please email us at our CONTACT US page.
PRACTICES
Business Law
Employment Law
General Litigation & Trial Practice
Health Law
Insurance Coverage
Professional Responsibility
Real Estate
